and get a loaf of bread.
And if they have eggs,
get a dozen.
You don't even need the punch line.
And so the programmer gets home with...
One more.
It takes me a while to remember all four of them.
None of them are any good, though.
That was the best.
The difference between an introverted programmer and an extroverted programmer.
Extroverted looks at your shoes when he pops teeth.
That's two of them.
This may be all I remember.
Anybody else know any other programmer jokes?
What's the difference between a professional programmer and a large pizza?
A large pizza can beat a family of four.
Anybody else?
How many programmers does it take to change a light bulb?
That's a hardware problem.
There are 10 times the people in the world.
Those that don't say binary.
And those that don't.
That's four. That's four. That's all I'm required to know.
Thank you.